Passport of Satan
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
Please, please, say yes!!
Why not? I need the money with in 3 days.
No means no!
But Bell Cop is very famous, it will surely be sold out in but three days.
That's it! I'll just have to borrow the money secretly and return it in 3 days.
What a genius idea!
Nobita! Why do you want to steal money from my purse, little thief?
Mum's too mean to me!
She said I'm a little thief and will become an improper man.
Well, I can't blame her. You tried to steal the money, after all.
Alright, I've made up my mind!
I'll become an evilest person in the whole world...
...and show her just how bad her son can be!
Give me a gadget that does the job!
Sorry, but I have no such gadgets!
What's this?
Oh no! He pulled out the Passport of Satan!
This Passport is so worst that...
All you need to do is show this passport to someone and then....
... even if you sin a wickedest sin, you won't be punished back by karma.
No matter what sins I commit...?
Yes, I'm afraid...
You just show them and it does the job?
Indeed, that is correct.
I've always wanted a gadget like this!
Gimme that back!
Doraemon, don't be so closed-minded!
You stole it from me!
It's alright, you can have it and do whatever you want!
Just what do you think you're doing?>
You can even take that wallet, I don't mind.
But I need only ¥1000.
Hurray!
I can now do whatever I want!
I kicked that dustbin and dirtied the road.
Do you have any problem with that?
Not at all.
Feels good!
Damn you, Nobita!
Please forgive me, Nobita.
Teacher, I'll cheat in next exam.
Do it properly.
Hi, Shizuka-chan!
Oh, it's you Nobita-kun.
I can take a nice peek of your panties...
Yay!
I can now buy Bell Cop manga at last.
Bell Cop
Oh, I don't have to pay any money, as long as I have this passport.
I'm going to take it home.
Why not? Of course you can.
Please visit again.
Yay! I stole it boldly! I'm now like Lupin the phantom thief!
But the owner of the store loses ¥350.
It's quite costly.
I do feel bad for him.
Did you enjoyed doing evil deeds?
Well, yes.
Bell Cop
Now I'm gonna read it!
I feel bad for Mum though.
She has hard time at home.
Bell Cop is so much fun!
I'm sorry, Nobita!
Oh no, you're a pervert!
Maybe I went too overboard...
You're so weak that you're sad about it.
But!
You're so wimpy!
It's impossible for you to ever be evil.
I won't work for you, Clumsy! Wimp! Coward!
Shadduppppp!
Where are you going?
Are you going to pay me?
Bye!
Oh, there you are!
Need a hand?
Here have this back.
Are you done, already?
I'll return Mum's ¥1000.
That's all, right?
I forgot to return the book!
Ah, damn!
It's impossible to for you to be evil. See?
I forgot to get ¥650 back from the shopkeeper, the manga was only ¥350!
I need my ¥650 back!